(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
んらああああ
Nraaaaaa
みんな、おりゅ～？
Is everyone here~?
なのなのなう！
Nano-nano now!
お菓子の国の お姫様
The princess of the Candy Kingdom
とびきりプリティな 0歳児
An exceptionally pretty 0-year-old
ピアノだって弾けるんだし
I can even play the piano
赤ちゃんじゃないのらよ！
I'm not a baby, nano-ra!
ワガママだって言うけれど
They say I'm selfish
ルーナはお姫様なのだから
But Luna is a princess, after all
ルーナイト達も 執事も
LuKnights and butlers alike
いちいちうるさいのら！
Are so noisy all the time, nano-ra!
さあ、ルーナイト達！
Now, LuKnights!
準備はできたのら？
Are you ready?
出陣なのら～！
To the battlefield, nano-ra~!
パフェもシュワシュワも 早く用意するのら！
Hurry up and prepare the parfaits and fizzy drinks!
あれもこれも食べたいのら！
I want to eat this and that, nano-ra!
おいしいのは独り占め
I'll keep the tasty ones all for myself
まずいの苦いのは ルーナイト達に差し入れ！
I'll give the bad and bitter ones to the LuKnights!
チョコレートの噴水も
Chocolate fountains
キャンディの首飾りも
And candy necklaces too
素敵なのたくさんあるのら
There are so many wonderful things, nano-ra
どこからルーナのために集めてきてね♡
Collect them all for Luna from wherever they are♡
絶対絶対絶対約束 なのなのら！
Absolute, absolute, absolute promise! Nano-nano-ra!
まわる まわる まわる ルーナ
Spinning, spinning, spin-Luna
まわる まわる まわる ルーナ・ナ・ナ
Spinning, spinning, spin-Luna-na-na
ぐるぐる まわって もっと ぐるぐる まわって もっと
Round and round, spin more, round and round, spin more
ぐるぐる まわって みんな ぐるぐる まわって
Round and round, everyone, round and round
ぐるぐる まわって そらもっと ぐるぐる まわって もっと
Round and round, there, spin more, round and round, spin more
ぐるぐる まわって 笑って ずっと ぐるぐる まわルーナ
Round and round, laugh forever, round and round, spin-Luna
ぐるぐる地球は回り始め幾億年
Billions of years since the earth began its spinning
いつまでもこのまま
Continuing forever like this
回るみんなに幸せを... 幸せを...
Wishing happiness to everyone who spins... happiness...
まわり まわる まわる ルーナ
Spinning, spinning, spin-Luna
ますますマッス 社会が ぐるぐるま～... あれ？
More and more mass, society is spinning rou... huh?
ぐるぐる まわって もっと ぐるぐる まわって もっと
Round and round, spin more, round and round, spin more
ぐるぐる まわって みんな ぐるぐる まわって
Round and round, everyone, round and round
ぐるぐる 笑って もっと ぐるぐる 笑って もっと
Round and round, laugh more, round and round, laugh more
ぐるぐる 踊って みんな ぐるぐる 踊って もっと
Round and round, dance, everyone, round and round, dance more
ぐるぐる まわって...
Round and round...
もっともっと
More and more
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回って おんの～
Spinning round and round, onno~
ぐるぐる回る 回るおんの～ やぁ
Spinning around, spinning, onno~, yeah!
まんなかちてん
The center point
作詞・作曲・編曲：かめりあ
Lyrics/Composition/Arrangement: Camellia
いつもおとぎ話のお姫様
Always a princess from a fairy tale
みんなの輝くお月様
Everyone's shining moon
今日はお休みして
Taking a break today
重い王冠今はおいといて
Putting aside the heavy crown for now
どっちの私も
Will you come to love
好きになってくれますか
both sides of me?
どっちも欲しいから
I want both, so
まんなかにいたくなるの
I want to be in the center
スニーカーと
Changing into
シャツに着替えて
sneakers and a shirt
あるきだしたんだ
I've started walking
出発のアラームは
The departure alarm is...
新しい私
I'll play a new
奏でてあげる
version of myself for you
両腕を
Even if I fill
いっぱいにしても
my arms to the brim
ぎゅっとしたい
I want to hold it tight,
この気持ち入らない
this feeling won't fit
片っぽなんて選べない
I can't choose just one side
迷ってるなら
If you're lost...
まんなかなんだよ
It's right in the center
満開の青春
Youth in full bloom,
満腹に摂取
consuming until full
満天流星群
A sky full of meteors,
満足にheaven
a satisfying heaven
満面笑顔にして
With a face full of smiles,
満点すぎる思い出
memories that are more than perfect
まーまるな Happy day!!
A round Happy day!!
愛のまんなかで
At the center of love
プリンセスを
So much that
忘れるくらい
you almost forget the princess
胸まんたんに
I want to feel
きゅんとしてみたい
my heart full of excitement
どっちだって
Whichever it is,
ホントの私
it's the real me
瞬きしたら
If you blink,
君のどまんなか
I'll be right in your heart's center
まんなかに
Overlapping
かさねちてん
at the center
まんなかで
Distributing
くばるちてん
at the center
まんなかの
The center of
まんなかちてん
the center point
恋する女の子の
Taking the best parts
いいとこ取りで
of a girl in love
照れ隠した素直の今
Concealing my shyness, my honest self now
まんなかちてん
is the center point
跪きなさい
Kneel before me.
汝、この城の扉を叩いたものよ
You, who have knocked upon
the gates of this castle.
誓いなさい このルーナの盾となり矛となり
Swear to become both
shield and spear for this Luna.
夜はぐっすり眠れるまで
Until you can sleep soundly through the night...
ともにあることを！
Always be by my side!
捧げなさい！姫であるぞ！
Devote yourself! I am a princess!
守ってルーナイト
作詞・作曲：ナナホシ管弦楽団 編曲：岩見 陸
Protect me, Luna Knight
Lyrics/Comp: Nanahoshi Orchestra, Arrangement: Riku Iwami
止まるな！
Don't stop!
紅茶のカップ かちゃかちゃ鳴らさないってえらい！
You're doing great not clinking your teacup!
スコーンだって 零さず綺麗に食べてすごい！
It's amazing how you eat your scones neatly!
たまに王冠 どっちが前か間違っちゃうの かわいい！
It's cute how I sometimes forget which way my crown faces!
通ってよし！ なのら 開城～！
You may pass! Nanora! Open the gates~!
ルーナイト第一条！ 誰よりルーナが好きな人！
Rule 1! Someone who loves Luna most!
ルーナイト第二条！ シルクのお布団持ってきて！
Rule 2! Bring me a silk duvet!
ルーナイト第三条！ 三時のお茶会来れる人！
Rule 3! Someone who can come to the 3 PM tea party!
守れなかったら即制裁！
Immediate punishment if you fail to comply!
分かってほしいのら
I want you to understand, nanora
これも、帝王学を学ぶための
This too, is part of learning how to be a ruler
愛という名の…教育なのら～！
It's an... education in the name of love, nanora~!
守ってルーナイト 想ってくんないと
Protect me, Luna Knight, if you don't
プロムナードボイコット なのなのら！
keep me in your thoughts, I'll boycott the promenade!
手の甲に 忠誠誓うの？ チュッ
Swearing loyalty on the back of my hand? Mwah
ガラスの靴 履かせてワルツ！
Put on my glass slippers and waltz!
守ってルーナイト 甘えてくんないと
Protect me, Luna Knight, if you don't let me be spoiled...
ブラウニーにキャンディー どれだけあってもね
Brownies and candies, no matter how many,
君がいなきゃだって！
it's no good without you!
みんな 心して
Everyone, pay attention
捧げなさい！姫であるぞ！
Devote yourself! I am a princess!
守ってルーナイト 想ってくんないと
Protect me, Luna Knight, if you don't
プロムナードボイコット なのなのら！
keep me in your thoughts, I'll boycott the promenade!
永遠の 忠誠この指に チュッ
Eternal loyalty on this finger, mwah
ガラスの靴 履かせてワルツ！
Put on my glass slippers and waltz!
守ってルーナイト かまってくんないと
Protect me, Luna Knight, if you don't give me attention...
ブラウニーにキャンディー どれだけあってもね
Brownies and candies, no matter how many,
君がいなきゃだって！
it's no good without you!
みんな 心して
Everyone, pay attention
捧げなさい！姫であるぞ！
Devote yourself! I am a princess!
おな～い！
Onai!
みんな、おな～！
Everyone, onai~!
ホロライブ４期生 姫森ルーナなのら～！
I'm hololive 4th gen Himemori Luna, nanora~!
今日はルーナの 生誕祭ライブー！イェーイ！
Today is Luna's Birthday Live! Yay!
みんな来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you everyone for coming!
今日のハッシュタグはこちら！
Today's hashtag is this!
デデン！
Deden!
＃姫森ルーナ生誕ライブ2025
#HimemoriLunaBirthdayLive2025
これでいっぱいツイートしてください！
Please tweet a lot with this!
えー、みんな、おなタンのオリ曲メドレーどうだった？
So, everyone, how was the birthday original song medley?
可愛かった？ふむふむ。ふむふむ。可愛い可愛い。わかってたのら。
Was it cute? I see, I see. Cute, cute. I knew it-nora.
そして、今日のステージを見てください。ジャジャジャジャーン。
And now, please look at today's stage. Ta-da!
すげー、雲だらけ。
Wow, it's full of clouds.
あっちのさ、この雲の向こう、何があるのらなかな？
I wonder what's over there, beyond these clouds-nora?
みんな予想してみて。
Everyone, try to guess.
そして今日のライブテーマは、「Luna RebirthDay」の。
And the theme of today's live is "Luna RebirthDay."
どんな意味があるのか。はてさて。
I wonder what it means.
そして、待ってルーナイト。
And, wait a second Lu-knights.
歌ってるときに、うな、ルーたん、大変身しました。
While singing, Lu-tan underwent a huge transformation.
みんな気づいてくれたのら？
Did everyone notice-nora?
100万人記念で新モデルになりました。
I got a new model to celebrate reaching 1 million subscribers.
そして、ポルーナイトがうな、ルーたんに魔法をかけてくれたのらよね。
And Polu-night cast a spell on Lu-tan, didn't they?
ポルーナイト、ありが...
Polu-night, thank yo...
姫ー！
Princess!
およ？
Oh?
姫ー！
Princess!
およ？どこにいんのらな？
Oh? Where are you-nora?
わー！この雲の向こうにいます！ポリスです！
Whoa! I'm beyond these clouds! It's Polu!
そうなのらね。ねえねえ、私の新しい姿どう？どう？
I see-nora. Hey, hey, how's my new look? How is it?
え、めっちゃ可愛いですわ。
Eh, it's incredibly cute.
え、ホント？ホント？
Eh, really? Really?
せっかくだから、姫の以前の姿を出して比較してみましょう。
Since we're here, let's bring out the Princess's previous look and compare them.
あ、いいねいいねいいね。
Ah, that's a good idea.
ホッ！
Hup!
どこどこどこ。あ、光ってる。出た、パネルが出そう。出た出た出た。
Where, where? Ah, it's glowing. The panel is coming out. It's out!
え、見てどう？
Look, what do you think?
ええ、ではまずは足元から見ていきましょう。
Well, let's start by looking at the feet.
はい。
Yes.
おお、すご。あ、神崎さん、いい感じですよ、これ。
Wow, amazing. Ah, Kanzaki-san, this is looking good.
どうだどうだ？
How is it? How is it?
おお、なんかこれ、影の感じとか変わった。
Oh, it looks like things like the shadows have changed.
変わった？変わった変わった？
Changed? Changed, changed?
あー、スカートとか、質感が変わったね。
Ah, the texture of the skirt and all has changed.
おやおや。おー、可愛いね。
Oh my. Oh, it's cute.
いい感じいい感じ。
Looking good, looking good.
待って、ここらへん、ここらへんとか待って。これ、加圧トレーニングの効果、出てるんじゃない？
Wait, look around here. Isn't the effect of the pressure training showing?
え？出てる？うな、出てる？
Eh? Is it showing? Is it showing on me?
最近、加圧トレーニングしてる？
Have you been doing pressure training lately?
やってるよ、パーソナルだけどな。
I am, although it's personal training.
あ、そうそう、後ろ向いて、後ろ後ろ。
Ah, right, turn around, let's see the back.
え、後ろ？およ？
Eh, the back? Oh?
おー！これこれ！え、見てこれ、髪の毛の揺れ。あとシルエット。これめっちゃいいじゃん。ふわふわ。
Oh! This, this! Look at the hair movement. And the silhouette. This is great. Fluffy.
ふわふわ。えへえへ。
Fluffy. Hehe.
あとね、うな、ルーたんの手も見てほしいのらな。
And also, I want you to look at Lu-tan's hands too-nora.
わー！おててが、まあ小さくて可愛いね！
Wow! The hands are, well, so small and cute!
いいでしょ。手相もいい感じ。
Right? The palm lines look good too.
手相。手相ね。うん。
Palm lines. Palm lines, I see. Yeah.
あと顔見て。
Also, look at the face.
あ、お顔。パネルと比べるのはちょっと難しいんだけど、斜めから見た時の、フェイスラインとか変わったね。超可愛いじゃん。
Ah, the face. It's hard to compare with the panel, but the face line from an angle has changed. It's super cute.
変わった？超可愛いじゃん。
Changed? Super cute, right?
えへえへ。パパ、ありがとの。
Hehe. Thanks, Papa.
まあ、ぜひみんなもね、過去の3D配信と見比べてほしいのらな。
Well, I'd like everyone to compare it with my past 3D streams-nora.
ねえねえ、ポルーナイト？
Hey, hey, Polu-night?
質問があるのだけど、そっちの雲の向こうってどうなってるのら？
I have a question, what's it like beyond those clouds over there-nora?
舞踏会の会場あるよ。来る？
There's a ballroom venue. Want to come?
え？マジ？
Eh? Seriously?
おいでよ！馬車ー！
Come on! Carriage!
え、馬車？
Eh, carriage?
わあ、めっちゃ光ってる。うわわわわ。
Wow, it's glowing so much. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
うわわわわ。でけー！これムーンギャラクシーの時、ステージにくっついてた馬車なのらよ。
Whoa! It's huge! This is the carriage from Moon Galaxy-nora.
というわけで、姫。乗っちゃってください。
So, Princess. Please get on.
乗れるの？
Can I get on?
乗ってください。
Please get on.
乗るのらな。
I'm getting on-nora.
うわあ、すごい！中も豪華なのら。ちょっとここ座ってみるのら。よいしょ。
Wow, amazing! The inside is so luxurious-nora. I'll try sitting here. Heave-ho.
ルーナイトの人形もあるのらね。すごい。
There's even a Lu-knight doll-nora. Amazing.
姫、準備はオッケーですかー？
Princess, are you ready?
バッチリだ！出発進行なのらー！
Perfect! Full speed ahead-nora!
よし！飛びますよ！行けー！
Alright! We're taking off! Go!
うお、動いた！わあ、進むぞ。
Whoa, it moved! Wow, we're going.
すげー、この馬車飛んでるのら！
Amazing, this carriage is flying-nora!
よし、よいしょよいしょ。こっち見てみよう。
Alright, heave-ho, heave-ho. Let's look over here.
うわあ、すごい。星と雲がめちゃくちゃ綺麗なのリ。
Wow, incredible. The stars and clouds are so beautiful-nori.
わあ、眺め最高なのらね。
Wow, the view is the best-nora.
ガタンゴトンと馬車はいいのら。
Click-clack, the carriage is nice-nora.
こっちからも見てみるのらね。よいしょ、よいしょ。
Let's look from this side too-nora. Heave-ho, heave-ho.
こっちもすごい。眺め最高。わあ、いい感じなのら。高いなー、でもここ。
This side is amazing too. The view is the best. Wow, it feels good-nora. It's high up here, though.
てかポルーナイトさ、このまま進んだら目の前のデカい雲とぶつかるのらけどさ、大丈夫なのら？
By the way Polu-night, if we keep going like this, we'll crash into that big cloud in front of us. Is it okay-nora?
進んで、向こうが何も見えないのなのよ。
Moving forward, I can't see anything ahead.
やあ、ご安心ください。このポルナイトにお任せあれ。
Hey, please rest assured. Leave it to this Paul Knight.
姫、少々揺れますぞ。しっかり捕まってて下さい。
Princess, it's going to shake a bit. Please hold on tight.
大丈夫？
Is it okay?
え、大丈夫これ本当に？
Wait, is this really okay?
行きますぞー！
Here we go!
本当に大丈夫！？
Are you really okay!?
ヤバいんじゃないの？雲来てるよ！
Isn't this bad? The clouds are coming!
うわああああああ！
Uwaaaaaaaa!
あたし今最上級に可愛いの
Right now, I'm the cutest in the world
君に振られて
After you dumped me
最上級に可愛いの
I'm the cutest in the world
これが乙女の逆襲だ！
This is a girl's counterattack!
作詞・作曲：コレサワ
Lyrics/Composition: Koresawa
もう気づいてるかも
You might have already noticed
しれないけど言うわ
But I'll say it anyway
あたしね 今とても
You know, right now, I'm extremely
かわいい
Cute
君が始めた恋
The love you started
君が終わらすなんて
That you're the one to end it
なんだそれ 泣いちゃうぞ
What's up with that? I'm gonna cry
かわいい
Cute
あたしの連絡だけ
Only my messages
通知OFFにしてたなんて
To think you turned off notifications for them
友達から聞いたよ
I heard it from a friend
連絡しすぎだって
Saying I message too much
君が不安にさせるからじゃん
It's because you make me feel insecure
もう気にしてないけど
I don't care anymore though
だって今
Because right now
君に振られて最上級に可愛いの
After you dumped me, I'm the cutest in the world
自分史上1番ときめき放つわ
I'm radiating the most excitement in my history
最上級に可愛いの
I'm the cutest in the world
認めなよ これが乙女の逆襲だ！
Admit it, this is a girl's counterattack!
さすがに失恋直後は涙でぐちゃぐちゃで
As expected, right after the breakup, I was a mess of tears
かわいくなかったけど
And I wasn't cute at all, but...
君が泣かせたのに
Even though you're the one who made me cry
雑なさよならだった
It was such a clumsy goodbye
なんだそれ 泣いちゃうぞ
What's up with that? I'm gonna cry
かわいい
Cute
二人しか知らないって言ってた話だって
Even the stories you said only the two of us knew
どうしてあの子も知ってるの
Why does that girl know them too?
別れてよかったなんて思わせないで欲しかった
I wish you hadn't made me think it was a good thing we broke up
好きだったから
Because I loved you
君に振られて最上級に可愛くなりました
After you dumped me, I became the cutest in the world
むしろありがと 最上級に可愛くなったってねえ言って 知って
Actually, thank you. Hey, tell me and know that I've become the cutest in the world
あいつがなんか可愛くなったってねえ聞いて
Hey, listen to people saying that girl has somehow become cute
君に振られて最上級に可愛いの
After you dumped me, I'm the cutest in the world
自分史上1番ときめき放つわ
I'm radiating the most excitement in my history
最上級に可愛いの
I'm the cutest in the world
認めなよ これが乙女の逆襲だ！
Admit it, this is a girl's counterattack!
最上級に可愛いの
I'm the cutest in the world
君に振られて最上級に可愛いの
After you dumped me, I'm the cutest in the world
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a devoted Cinderella!
作詞：Orca (SUPA LOVE)
作曲：Daiki Shiobara (SUPA LOVE)
Lyrics: Orca (SUPA LOVE)
Composition: Daiki Shiobara (SUPA LOVE)
退屈な月曜日
A boring Monday
あなたの香りで目覚めるの
I wake up to your scent
纏ったトップノート
The top note I'm wearing
そうよ 秘密の物語なの
That's right, it's a secret story
うまくリプライできない
I can't reply well
震えるハート 躊躇い 恥じらい 空回り
Trembling heart, hesitation, shyness, and spinning my wheels
誘うファンタジー 重なっちゃうくらい一途だもん
Inviting fantasy, I'm so devoted that we overlap
あなたに夢中です
I'm crazy about you
Ah バズっちゃバズっちゃやんだ！
Ah, it's viral, it's viral, oh no!
ねえ かまってかまって もっと！
Hey, pay attention to me more!
誰もがあなたを狙っちゃう
Everyone is aiming for you
ウィンクひとつでメロメロにさせちゃって
Making everyone head over heels with a single wink
こっちの気も知らないで
Without even knowing how I feel
もー！バズっちゃバズっちゃやんだ
Geez! It's viral, it's viral, oh no!
ねえ 射抜いて射抜いて ずっと
Hey, shoot through my heart forever
いつでもあなたに惚れ中
I'm always in love with you
誰よりあなたの特別でいたいの
I want to be more special to you than anyone else
…たいの
...want to be.
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a devoted Cinderella!
どんな道が待ってても
No matter what road awaits,
ガラスのヒールで駆けてくよ
I'll run in glass heels.
魔法が解けて醒めない夢を
A dream that doesn't end even when the magic breaks,
あなたにあげるのなだ
I'll give to you, nanoda.
だから絶対 負けない
So I'll never give up.
脈打つビート
A pulsing beat,
純愛したい まっすぐに
I want a pure love, straight ahead.
想うエンパシー 伝わっちゃうくらい
My empathy is felt so much it transmits,
本気だもん
because I'm serious.
まさしく無敵ですっ
I'm truly invincible!
Ah ハマってハマっていいよ
Ah, it's okay to get hooked, get hooked.
ねえ ディグってディグってギュンと
Hey, dig in, dig in, and get a heart-squeeze.
恋する乙女は変幻自在
A girl in love is ever-changing.
「キレイ」も「ビューティー」も欲張りに励めば
If I strive greedily for both 'Pretty' and 'Beauty',
輝く自分になるの
I'll become a sparkling version of myself.
さあ！ハマってハマっていいよ
Now! It's okay to get hooked, get hooked.
ねえ 気づいて気づいてちゃんと
Hey, notice me, notice me properly.
まだまだ乙女は日進月歩
A girl still makes steady progress every day.
世界で一番のドキドキがほしいの
I want the biggest heart-throbs in the world.
あなただけはプリンセスです
I'm your one and only princess.
I love you!
I need you!
Ah 「好き」って「好き」ってなんで
Ah, why is it 'I love you', 'I love you'...
そう「スキ」って「スキ」っていうの
Yes, why do we say 'I like you', 'I like you'?
けなげなココロは困惑中
My brave heart is currently confused.
愛しさ膨らんでこんなにも苦しいの
Love swells and it hurts this much.
今すぐこっちに微笑って
Smile this way right now.
Ah バズっちゃバズっちゃやだ
Ah, I don't want it to go viral, go viral.
ねえ かまってかまってもっと
Hey, pay attention, pay attention to me more.
誰もがあなたを狙っちゃう
Everyone is aiming for you.
ウインクひとつでメロメロにさせちゃって
Make them head over heels with a single wink.
あたしの気も知らないで！
Without even knowing how I feel!
もう！バズっちゃバズっちゃやだ
Geez! I don't want it to go viral, go viral.
ねえ 射抜いて射抜いてずっと
Hey, shoot through my heart, shoot through it forever.
いつでもあなたに奔放中
I'm always running wild for you.
誰よりあなたの特別でいたいの
I want to be more special to you than anyone else.
あたしで正解かな？ 許してね
Am I the correct answer? Forgive me.
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a devoted Cinderella!
オトメロディー
Oto Melody
スキスキスー フワフワフー
Suki-suki-suu, Fuwa-fuwa-fuu
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
This feeling is a Mero-Melody.
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but it's not a dream.
お願いね マイメロディ
Please, My Melody.
オトナじゃない オトメです
I'm not an adult, I'm a maiden.
恋するのがお仕事です
Falling in love is my job.
君の名前つぶやくと ドキドキするの
My heart flutters when I whisper your name.
聞き分けない この胸が
This heart of mine won't listen,
歌い出して止まらない
it starts singing and won't stop.
上手じゃなくてゴメンナサイ
I'm sorry I'm not very good at it.
だけど聞いて とどけ
But please listen, may it reach you.
マイメロディ マイメロディ
My Melody, My Melody.
星空を越えて 君の夢 守るリボン
A ribbon that crosses the starry sky to protect your dreams.
マイメロディ
My Melody.
ハート見つけたなら
If I find your heart,
ぐるぐる巻きしちゃうからね
I'll wrap it all up.
Wow wow wow 覚悟しといて
Wow wow wow, be prepared.
嘘じゃない
I'm not lying.
オトナじゃない オトメです
I'm not an adult, I'm a maiden.
泣いたりだってしちゃいます
I even cry sometimes.
女の子って魔法で 作られたの
Girls were made by magic.
スキスキスー フワフワフー
Suki-suki-suu, Fuwa-fuwa-fuu
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
This feeling is a Mero-Melody.
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but it's not a dream.
お願いね マイメロディ
Please, My Melody.
キライじゃない ってゆーかスキ
I don't hate you—I mean, I love you.
スナオになんてなれません
I just can't be honest.
君の笑顔見るだけで フニャフニャするの
Just seeing your smile makes me go all soft.
それなのにー それなのに！
And yet—and yet!
憎まれ口 撃ちまくり
I keep shooting off insults.
ひとりになって落ち込んで
Then I get depressed when I'm alone,
枕パンチ！！
pillow punch!!
だから
So...
マイメロディ マイメロディ
My Melody, My Melody.
本当の気持ち 風になって 結びリボン
My true feelings turn into the wind, a tied ribbon.
マイメロディ
My Melody.
歌えオトメゴコロ
Sing, maiden's heart.
オトメゴコロ
A maiden's heart
来る来る恋 つかまえちゃえは
If I catch the love that's coming
WOW WOW WOW 逃がさないから
WOW WOW WOW because I won't let it go
ここへ来て
Come here
キライじゃない ツライです (T-T)
I don't hate it, it's just painful (T-T)
真っ赤にだってなっちゃいます
I'll even turn bright red
女の子って不思議で 作られたの
Girls are made of wonders
とどけ
Reach...
マイメロディー マイメロディー
My Melody, My Melody
星空を越えて 君の夢 守るリボン
A ribbon that crosses the starry sky and protects your dreams
マイメロディー ハート見つけたなら
My Melody, if I find a heart
グルグル巻きにしちゃうからね
I'll wrap it up tight
WOW WOW WOW 覚悟しといて
WOW WOW WOW, be prepared
嘘じゃない
It's not a lie
オトナじゃない オトメです
I'm not an adult, I'm a maiden
泣いたりだってしちゃいます
I even do things like crying
女の子って魔法で 作られたの
Girls are made of magic
スキススキースー フワフワフー
Love, love, love, fluffy
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
This feeling, Mero-Melody
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but not a dream
お願いね マイメロディ
Please, My Melody
マイメロディ
My Melody
わあー！
Waaah!
ということで！
And so!
最上級に可愛いのと
The most adorable one,
一途なシンデレラ
Devoted Cinderella,
あとオトメロディー 3曲連続で歌いました！
And Otomerody—I sang three songs in a row!
いぇーい！
Yay!
雲が晴れたステージって こうなってるのなのね！
So this is what the stage looks like when the clouds clear!
すげー！
Amazing!
でっけー！
It's huge!
舞踏会みたいなのなのね！
It's like a ballroom!
あ、ここ見て！
Oh, look here!
シャンデリアがあるのなー！
There's a chandelier!
ザ・舞踏会 ダンスするって場所なのなのね！
It's a place for "The Ballroom" dancing!
あと
And also,
お城の上の方ってこうなってたんだ！
so this is what the top of the castle looked like!
見て！
Look!
すごい可愛い！
It's so cute!
しかもこれ、天窓じゃん！
Moreover, these are skylights!
豪華なのなのねー！
It's so luxurious!
すごい！
Amazing!
あ、待って、ルナリバースデーの看板もあるのな！
Oh, wait, there's even a "Luna RebirthDay" sign!
今日はルナリバースデーだからなのな！
That's because today is Luna RebirthDay!
見て見て、すごい可愛い！
Look, look, it's so cute!
お？なになになに？
Oh? What, what, what?
最高だったよー！
That was the best!
え、ホロナイト？
Eh, Horo-knight?
ホロナイトじゃないかーい！
It's a Horo-knight!
実はね、姫にはまだ隠された姿が残されているのですよ！
Actually, Princess, there is still a hidden form remaining for you!
え、なっ、なんなのな？
Eh, wha, what is it?
ホロナイトの魔法で そのお姿にしてみせましょう！
With Horo-knight magic, let me show you that form!
え、なになになに？
Eh, what what what?
はーっ！タケタケタケター！
Hah! Take-take-take-ta!
じゃじゃーん！
Ta-da!
わあ、すごい！可愛い！
Wow, amazing! Cute!
新しいヘアスタイルなのなー！
It's a new hairstyle!
ホロナイトがプレゼントしてくれたのなのね！
The Horo-knight gave it to me as a present!
ふふふ！
Hehe!
よし、じゃあこの新しい髪型で歌っちゃうのなー！
Alright, then I'll sing with this new hairstyle!
あなたのアイドル
Your idol
サインはB！
The sign is B!
日小町! フッフー!!
Hikomachi! Woo-hoo!!
ようやく会えたね 嬉しいね
Finally we met, I'm so happy
待ち遠しくて足をバッタバタしながら
While flapping my feet impatiently
今日楽しみで寝れなかったよ
I couldn't sleep because I was looking forward to today
緊張なんかしてる場合じゃない
It's no time to be nervous
1分1秒 無駄になんてできない
Not a single minute or second can be wasted
さあ 始めましょう
Now, let's begin
君も！君も！君も！ お待たせさま
You! And you! And you! Sorry for the wait
手を鳴らせ いらっしゃいませ
Clap your hands, welcome
「大好き」が集まる場所へようこそ
Welcome to the place where "love" gathers
日常はクロークの中
Daily life is in the cloakroom
ここに来たなら踊らにゃ 損 損
If you come here, it's a loss if you don't dance
人がいようがいまいが関係ない
It doesn't matter if people are there or not
会場が大きい小さいとか気にしない
I don't care if the venue is big or small
ちゃんと見えてる
I can see clearly
君のサイリウム！
Your glow sticks!
今はフッーと吹けば飛ぶような
Right now, like something that would fly away if you blew on it
小さな小さな才能だけど
It's a tiny, tiny talent, but...
私を推してくれるのなら
If you're going to support me...
If you're going to support me
爆レスをあげる
I'll give you an explosive response
あなたのアイドル
Your idol
サインはＢ！
The sign is B!
(B小町！ フッフー！)
(B-Komachi! Fu-fu-!)
あいつは俺が育てたって
Saying "I'm the one who raised her"
近い将来　自慢してほしいよ
I want you to brag about it in the near future
こうしちゃいられない
We can't just stay like this
君と！君と！今を！
With you! With you! This moment!
楽しまなきゃ
We've got to enjoy it
引きこもりも人見知りも
Whether you're a shut-in or shy
普段と違う顔見せてよ
Show me a different side of you
みんな兄弟　調子どうだい？
Everyone's a sibling, how's it going?
なりふり構わずに
Without caring about appearances
他人に笑われていても関係ない
It doesn't matter if others laugh at you
周りがどうとかこうとか気にしない
Don't care about what's going on around you
主張強すぎ君のサイリウム
Your glowstick that's way too assertive
たとえ世界が私を拒んで
Even if the world rejects me
独りぼっちを感じたとしても
And even if I feel all alone
あなたが味方でいてくれたら
If you are on my side
怖いものはないよ
There's nothing to be afraid of
(B小町！ フッフー！)
(B-Komachi! Fu-fu-!)
見てよ見てよ何かが始まる
Look, look, something is starting
君との物語が
A story with you
嗚呼なんて素晴らしい景色だ
Oh, what a wonderful view
客席が居ようがいまいが関係ない
It doesn't matter if there are empty seats
会場が大きい小さいとか気にしない
Don't care if the venue is big or small
ちゃんと見えてる君のサイリウム
I can clearly see your glowstick
今はふーっと吹けば飛ぶような
Right now, it's like it would blow away with a puff
小さな小さな才能だけど
It's a tiny, tiny talent, but...
私を
If you're going to...
推してくれるのなら
...support me
あなたが味方でいてくれたら
If you are on my side
爆レスをあげる
I'll give you an explosive response
あなたのアイドル
Your idol
サインはＢ！
The sign is B!
(フッフー！)
(Fu-fu-!)
(フッフッフー！)
(Fu-fu-fu-!)
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
Won't let romance scandals escape
消してあげる
I'll erase them for you
宣誓！私が大統領になったら
Oath! If I become President...
人の男にちょっかいかける女は島流しにします
...women who mess with other people's men will be exiled!
宣誓！私が大統領になったら
Oath! If I become President...
いやただの友達だよ～って誤魔化す奴はヘソから電気を流します
...people who dodge with "No, we're just friends~" will have electricity run through their navels!
だ・だ・だ・大胆不敵　センセーショナルクローズアップ
D-D-D-Daring and fearless, sensational close-up
ド・ド・ド・Don't cry　やるぜ徹底的にリサーチだ
D-D-D-Don't cry, I'll do it, I'll research thoroughly
大嫌い？しょうがない？
Hate it? Can't be helped?
クズは病気ね バイバイバイ
Scumbags are a disease, bye bye bye
権力！財産！地位名声！！ なんにもないけど裁きたいでしょ？
Power! Wealth! Status and fame!! I have nothing, but you want to judge, right?
だ・だ・だ・大統領になったらね
D-D-D-If I become President...
まずは君を捕まえるわ
...first, I'll capture you
濡れたタオルで 洗いざらい吐かせるね
With a wet towel, I'll make you spill everything
誰ですか あの女
Who is that woman?
ダメですか そうですか
No good? I see
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
Won't let romance scandals escape
消してあげる
I'll erase them for you
シル・ヴ・プレプレプレジデント
S'il vous plaî-plaî-plaî-President
宣誓！私が大統領になったら
Oath! If I become President...
ただの仕事の付き合いだよって言う奴は二度と働けなくしてやります
...people who say "It's just a work relationship" will never be able to work again!
宣誓！以下略！
Oath! Et cetera!
いや向こうが強引でさ～っていう男の口にはレジンを流し込んで固めてやります！
To men who say "Well, she was being pushy~," I'll pour resin into their mouths and harden it!
み・み・み・密着まるで ドン・ファン気取りスキャンダラス
C-C-C-Close contact, just like acting like Don Juan, scandalous
ま・ま・ま・末端価格 甲斐性なしのスクープね
L-L-L-Low-end price, a scoop from someone with no resourcefulness
愛はない？理由じゃない
No love? That's not a reason
悪くないのに はいはいはい
I'm not bad, but... yeah, yeah, yeah
軽薄！脳能！ビシャアシアア！！ なんにもないとがありえないでしょ？
Frivolous! Brain power! Bisha-ashiaa!! It's impossible to have nothing, right?
だ・だ・だ・大統領になってもね
D-D-D-Even if I become President...
たぶん君は変わらないね
...you probably won't change
しらっととぼけて
Playfully feigning ignorance...
のらりくらりかわすのね
...you dodge it aimlessly, don't you?
デートですか こんばんは
Is it a date? Good evening
本気ですか そうですか
Are you serious? I see
情熱とは不注意 微熱も
Passion is carelessness, and slight fevers too...
消してしまいたい
...I want to erase them
One, two, three!
だ・だ・だ・大統領になったらね
If I become the pre-pre-pre-president
マジで君を捕まえるね
I'll definitely capture you
濡れたタオルで
With a wet towel
洗いざらい吐かせるね
I'll make you confess everything
（ど・ど・ど！）
(Do-do-do!)
どこですか今あんた
Where are you right now?
見っけちゃったバレちゃった
Found you, you're busted
夜道にはご用心さよなら
Watch out on the night roads, goodbye
代わりに銃声
A gunshot instead
シル・ヴ・プレプレプレジデント
S'il vous pre-pre-pre-president
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
貴方のことも忘れたいこと 悲しいこと あるのかしらね
I wonder if there are things about you,
things I want to forget, or sad things.
知らない映画なのに涙を流すのは ドラマチックが足りてないからよ
The reason I cry at a movie I don't know
is because there's not enough drama.
そんな風にもつかないこと くだらないこと 考えてばかりね
I'm always thinking about things that
don't make sense, silly things.
雨が上がれば相も変わらず不機嫌も 誰かさんのものになるんでしょう
When the rain stops, the bad mood will
probably belong to someone else as usual.
そっかつのファンデーションも全部 恋のためよ
Even all that hasty foundation is
for the sake of love.
なんて一体全体どうしてどうして なぜなぜハテナ
Why on earth, why, why, why, a question mark?
不安定な勝手などこまでゆくの 貴方一切合切放り去っても
Unstable and selfish, how far will you go?
Even if you throw everything away.
冗談じゃないないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
It's no joke, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来たってどうにもならないぜ
Even when that time comes,
there's nothing I can do
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリー 加するだけ
Ambiguous truths only add to the melancholy
私あっちゃこっちゃそっぽ向いて 今...
I'm looking this way and that, and now...
あー全然おかしなハートばかり
Ah, nothing but strange hearts
食指がピクリともしないわ
My appetite doesn't even twitch
地団駄のない感情放っておいたって
Even if I leave these feelings
without stomping my feet
策略なんてありゃせんのになぜ
There's no strategy at all, so why?
あーもう懲り懲りよ
Ah, I've had enough already
あたしの勝手なその気質も
Even my selfish temperament
じっとこらえて取り繕っておいては とうとう臨界点
Enduring it and keeping up appearances,
finally reaching the critical point.
回り出したテーブル全部忘れさせてよ
Make me forget all about the
tables that started spinning
だけど一体全体どうしてどうして なぜなぜハテナ
But why on earth, why, why, why, a question mark?
不安定な勝手な消えないままね 貴方一個錠ずつ食い違っても
Unstable and selfish, they won't disappear,
even if you're one tablet off.
冗談じゃないないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
It's no joke, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来たってどうにもならないぜ
Even when that time comes,
there's nothing I can do
不甲斐ないわ 感情なんて後回し 揺らすだけ
It's pathetic, putting feelings
aside and just shaking them
私堂々巡り目合っている街
A city where I'm going in
circles and our eyes meet
冗談じゃないないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
It's no joke, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来たってどうにもならないぜ
Even when that time comes,
there's nothing I can do
不甲斐ないわ 感情なんて後回し 揺らすだけ
It's pathetic, putting feelings
aside and just shaking them
私堂々巡り目合っている街
A city where I'm going in
circles and our eyes meet
アイアイヤ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Ai ai ya, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来たってどうにもならないぜ
Even when that time comes,
there's nothing I can do
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリー 加するだけ
Ambiguous truths only add to the melancholy
私あっちゃこっちゃそっぽ向いて 今
I'm looking this way and that, and now
さよなら人類
Sayonara Jinrui
二酸化炭素を吐き出して
Exhaling carbon dioxide
あの子が呼吸をしているよ
That girl is breathing
曇天模様の空の下
Under the cloudy sky
つぼみのままで揺れながら
Swaying while still a bud
野良犬は僕の骨くわえ
The stray dog holds my bone in its mouth
野性の力を試してる
Testing its wild power
路地裏に月が落ちてきて
The moon falls into the back alley
犬の目玉は四角だよ
The dog's eyes are square
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, for the first time, humanity...
木星についたよ
...reached Jupiter
ピテカントロプスになる日も
Even the day we become Pithecanthropus...
近づいたんだよ
...is drawing near
さよなら人類
Sayonara Jinrui (Goodbye Humanity)
あ～よぉ～
Ah~ yo~
アラビヤの笛の音響く
The sound of Arabian flutes echoes
町のはずれの夢のあと
Remnants of a dream on the outskirts of town
翼をなくしたペガサスが
A Pegasus that lost its wings
夜空にはしごかけている
Is putting a ladder up to the night sky
武器をかついだ兵隊さん
A soldier carrying a weapon
南に行こうとしてるけど
Is trying to head south, but...
サーベルの音はチャラチャラと
The jingling sound of the saber
町の空気を汚してる
Pollutes the town's air
今日 人類が初めて
Today, for the first time, humanity
木星についたよ
Reached Jupiter
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
Has drawn near, too
歌を忘れたカナリア
A canary that forgot how to sing
牛を忘れた牛小屋
A cowshed that forgot its cows
壊れた磁石をひろい集める
Collecting broken magnets
博士はまるはげさ
The doctor is completely bald
あのこは花火を打ち上げて
That girl sets off fireworks
この日が来たのを祝ってる
Celebrating that this day has come
冬の花火は強すぎて
Winter fireworks are too strong
ぼくらの体は砕け散る
And our bodies are shattered
ブーゲンビリアの木の下で
Under the bougainvillea tree
ぼくはあのこを探すけど
I search for that girl, but...
月の光に邪魔されて
Disturbed by the moonlight
あのこのかけらは見つからない
I can't find pieces of that girl
今日 人類が初めて
Today, for the first time, humanity
木星についたよ
Reached Jupiter
ついたー！
Reached it!
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
Has drawn near, too
今日 人類が初めて
Today, for the first time, humanity
木星についたよ
Reached Jupiter
おー、ついたー！
Oh, reached it!
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
Has drawn near, too
猿にはなりたくない
I don't want to become a monkey
壊れた磁石を砂浜で
Collecting broken magnets
ひろっているだけさ
On the sandy beach
今日 人類が初めて
Today, for the first time, humanity
木星についたよ
Reached Jupiter
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
Has drawn near, too
さよなら人類
Goodbye, humanity
さよなら
Goodbye
あ～
Ah~
サンドリヨン
作詞:orange 作曲:Dios/シグナルP
Cendrillon
Lyrics: orange  Composition: Dios/Signal-P
朝まで踊る 夢だけ見せて
Dance until morning, let me see only dreams
時計の鐘が解く魔法
The magic dissolved by the tolling of the clock
曖昧な指 誘う階段
Vague fingers, enticing stairs
三段飛ばしに跳ねていく
Leaping three steps at a time
馬車の中で震えていた
I was trembling inside the carriage
みじめな古着 めくりめぐれ夜の
Miserable old clothes, turning and turning, the night's
舞踏
Dance
見知らぬ顔
An unfamiliar face
見知らぬ顔探す
Searching for a face I don't recognize
囁くあの声が
That whispering voice
握り締めた刃　突き立て
Thrusting the blade I held tight
すべてを奪えと
Telling me to take it all
孤児（みなしご）集う城
The castle where orphans gather
笑み仮面に描いて
Drawing a smile on a mask
偽りの慈しみさえ
Even false affection
羽で包む　熾天使（セラフ）
Wrapped in wings, a Seraph
灰の中で
In the ashes
赤く溶けて
Melting into red
混じる硝子の靴
A glass slipper mixing in
今更帰る　震えているの
Returning now, I'm trembling
あなたが目をやる時計
The clock you glance at
靴脱ぎ踊る　スロープ抜けて
Taking off shoes and dancing, passing through the slope
喉まで伸びる指先で
With fingertips reaching for the throat
すくう雫
Scooping up droplets
口付けて
Kissing
走る衝動　背骨抜けていく
A running impulse passing through the spine
刹那
In a split second
鐘は鳴らさないで
Don't let the bells ring
あなたにひざまずき
Kneeling before you
まだダメと叫んだ
Shouting "Not yet"
右手が突き刺すサヨナラ
My right hand stabs with a "Goodbye"
消せない硝煙を
The inextinguishable gunpowder smoke
香水にまとう姫
A princess wearing it in perfume
強い瞳　僕の凍った
Strong eyes, my frozen...
仮面ごと打ち抜く
Piercing right through the mask
今も耳にあなたの吐息が
Even now your breath in my ear...
突き刺さるの遠い夢
Stabs like a distant dream
ステンドグラスごし
Through the stained glass
光る月が
The glowing moon
君にかぶせたベール
A veil placed over you
ドレス膝で裂いて
Tearing the dress at the knees
ティアラは投げ捨てて
Throwing away the tiara
見つめあう瞳と瞳が
Eyes meeting eyes
火花を放つ
Setting off sparks
孤独な魂が
Lonely souls
炎あげ惹かれあう
Drawn together by rising flames
その涙掬えないなら
If those tears can't be saved
まるで一人遊び
It's like playing alone
時よ止まれ今は
Time, stop now
あなたに酔いしれて
Being intoxicated by you
揺れる鼓動一つ一つを刻み付けてたい
Wanting to engrave every single swaying heartbeat
とどまれ熱く濡れ
Stay, hot and wet
打ち付ける高まりに
In the striking surge
これ以上は動けないよ
Can't move any more than this
まるで御伽噺
Like a fairy tale
みんな、ここからは大事な告知タイムなのらー！イェイイェイイェイ！
Everyone, from here on, it's important announcement time! Yay yay yay!
ポルポル、ポルポルはそこで見ててななね！イェイイェイイェイ！
Pol-Pol, Pol-Pol, watch from there! Yay yay yay!
では、まずはこちら！
Now, first up is this!
姫森ルーナ誕生日記念2025
Himemori Luna Birthday Celebration 2025
姫森ルーナ誕生日記念2025のグッズだっよー！イェイ！
It's the Himemori Luna Birthday Celebration 2025 goods! Yay!
ではね、こちら詳細見ていきましょう！
Now, let's look at the details!
ふたりのルーナ♡アクリルジオラマスタンド
Two Lunas Acrylic Diorama Stand
「ふたりのルーナ♡アクリルジオラマスタンド」なのらー！イラストは、トイロ先生に描いていただきました！
It's the "Two Lunas Acrylic Diorama Stand"! The illustration was drawn by Toiro-sensei!
前のね、髪型と、今回のルーナのね、新しい髪型のルーナが...
The previous hairstyle and Luna's new hairstyle for this time...
そして今回の生誕ライブのステージに登場しました！
And they appeared on the stage of this birthday live!
こちらはね、立体的なパーツが華やかな可愛い素敵な豪華仕様のジオラマスタンドになっておりまーす！
This is a diorama stand with a gorgeous, cute, and wonderful deluxe specification with 3D parts!
そして、次はこちら！
And next is this!
姫森ルーナぬいぐるみ♡守ってルーナイトver.
Himemori Luna Plushie: Protect You Lu-Knight ver.
「姫森ルーナぬいぐるみ♡見守ってルーナイトver.」！はい！
The "Himemori Luna Plushie: Watching Over You Lu-Knight ver."! Yes!
まずはこちら、届きました！
First, here it is!
「守ってルーナイト」の衣装のんなたんがぬいぐるみになりましたー！
Nna-tan in her "Mamotte LuKnight" outfit has become a plushie!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ぜひぜひ、みんなお家にお迎えして
By all means, everyone, please welcome her into your home
んなたんをね、守ってほしいのならよ！
and protect Nna-tan, okay!
そして、次はこちら！
And, next is this!
デデン！ルーナイト 2WAY バッグ！
Ta-da! LuKnight 2-Way Bag!
さっきのぬいぐるみもすっぽり入ってしまう
The plushie from before fits perfectly inside,
ルーナイトがアピールできるバッグになたにます
making it a bag that shows off your LuKnight pride!
バッグはね、なんとリュックにもなって超便利！
The bag can even be used as a backpack, so it's super convenient!
デザインに使用されているモチーフは、ルーナイト由来のもので統一しているので
The motifs used in the design are all derived from LuKnights,
バッグモードでもリュックモードでも、お好きな方で使ってください！
so please use it in either bag mode or backpack mode, whichever you prefer!
次は、こちら！
Next, is this!
デデン！ルーナイト カードホルダー！
Ta-da! LuKnight Card Holder!
ルーナイト型のカードホルダーです！
It's a LuKnight-shaped card holder!
チェキ風カードやホロカのカードも入れられちゃうので
You can put Cheki-style cards or Hololive Official Card Game cards in it,
ルーナイトのみんなはこっちもしっかり守ってくださいね！
so LuKnights, please make sure to protect this as well!
そして、次はこちら！
And, next is this!
デデン！ボイス！
Ta-da! Voice!
ASMRボイス 〜舞踏会の帰り道〜
ASMR Voice: On the Way Home from the Ball
今回はね、舞踏会をイメージした生誕祭ライブなので
Since today's birthday live is themed around a ball,
ルーナイトと帰路についたひとときをボイスにしました！
I made a voice recording of a moment spent on the way home with a LuKnight!
馬車の中という密室で、なんか急接近とかあっちゃうかも！？
In the private space of a carriage, maybe we'll get unexpectedly close!?
ということで、最後に改めてフルセットを見てみましょう！
So, let's take another look at the full set at the end!
こちら、フルセット購入特典は...
The bonus for purchasing the full set is...
デデン！オリジナルカード！
Ta-da! Original Card!
イラストはドイル先生で、表面がチェキ風のカードになってます
The illustration is by Noiler-sensei, and the front is a Cheki-style card.
裏面は招待状風のデザインになっていてオシャレななのら！
The back has an invitation-style design and is very stylish!
そして、通常バージョンのフルセット購入特典は
And the bonus for the standard version full set
箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカード！
is a Cheki-style bromide card with a foil-stamped replica signature!
そして、数量限定バージョンのフルセット購入特典は
And the bonus for the limited quantity version full set
直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードななのら！
is a Cheki-style bromide card with a handwritten signature!
みんなゲットしてほしいのら！
I hope everyone gets one!
グッズはね、配信終了後販売開始です！
The merch will be on sale after the stream ends!
そしてそして、もう一つ大事なお知らせがあります！
And, and, I have one more important announcement!
こちら！デデン！
This! Ta-da!
んなっしょいぱっしょん！
Nnashyoi Passion!
こちらをね、この後歌わせていただきます！
I'll be singing this song after this!
みんな大好き、んなっしょいという言葉を使っているのでね
It uses everyone's favorite word, "nnashyoi",
みんなこの後いっぱいんなっしょいしてな！
so everyone, do a lot of "nnashyoi" later!
この配信がね、終わったらMVも公開されます！
When this stream is over, the MV will also be released!
そして、MV公開後もメンゲンが今回初めてやることになったので
And I'll also be doing a members-only stream for the first time after the MV release,
こちらもお楽しみに！
so look forward to that too!
ではね、歌います！
Now, I'm going to sing!
んなっしょいぱっしょん！
Nnashyoi Passion!
なななな、きっとー
Na-na-na-na, surely—
別にオチとかねーのら！
There's no punchline!
ねぇのら！
Nee-no-ra!
んなっしょいぱっしょん
Nnashyoi Passion
むにゃいむにゃい 目をこする
Munyai munyai, rubbing eyes
囚われた城にパーフェクトな朝
A perfect morning in a captive castle
おないと お布団飛び出して
Jump out of the "O-Knight" futon
海へ行こう！
And let's go to the sea!
神様だって間違えるんだって
Even gods make mistakes
よくある話だそうです
So they say it's a common story
姫様にね 見とれちゃうんだって
I heard you'll be captivated by the princess
やれやれだのらね
Good grief, na-no-ra
夢を夢見て
Dreaming a dream
恋に恋して生きていたい
I want to live, being in love with love
だからこれでいいのら！
So this is fine, na-no-ra!
なななな、泣きたい
Na-na-na-na, I want to cry
腹はらいたい
My stomach hurts
心だって洗って変えるのら！
I'll wash and change my heart too, na-no-ra!
だから会いたい
So I want to meet you
その願いに いま約束の合言葉
With that wish, now for the promised watchword
いくよっ！んなっしょい！
Here we go! Nnashyoi!
まどろみもホラーな夜もあるけど
There are slumbering and horror nights, too
でもね んなっしょい！
But still, nnashyoi!
いつまでもみんな おゆからへいき！
Everyone can stay in the hot water forever!
まだ遊び足りねーのら！
I haven't had enough play yet, na-no-ra!
暗い 暗い 夜の中
In the dark, dark night
ティアラを外して 城を抜けたら
I take off my tiara and escape the castle
深い 深い 海に出て
And venture into the deep, deep sea
…バレてんの？グッドナイト
...Are you onto me? Good night
姫様はね わがままでなんて
That princesses are selfish...
お伽話 そうでしょ？
...is just a fairy tale, right?
何がなんだって 私なんだって
No matter what, I am me
これでいいのら！
And that's just fine-nora!
泣きたい 私でいたい！
I want to cry! I want to be myself!
どこへだって 向かって行けるのなら
If I can head toward anywhere
ならば さぁない この想いに
Then, to these feelings that won't fade
今 許される合言葉
Now, here's the password that's permitted
行くよっ！ なーっしょい！
Here we go! Nasshoi!
サンゴ礁 白い砂浜も綺麗 そこに なーっしょい！
The coral reefs and white sandy beaches are beautiful. To that, nasshoi!
なっしょい！ 輝く私
Nasshoi! The shining me
Q.帰る理由は？ A.そこに投げればねえのら！
Q. Why go home? A. If it's there, then there is no reason-nora!
んなあああい！
Nnaaaai!
リピートアフターミー！
Repeat after me!
なっしょい！ なっしょい！
Nasshoi! Nasshoi!
せーのっ！
Ready, go!
なっしょい！ なっしょい！ もう一回！
Nasshoi! Nasshoi! One more time!
なっしょい！ なっしょい！ いいねー！
Nasshoi! Nasshoi! Nice!
熱い視線が集中
All eyes are on me
ハラハラする心に夢中 だから
I'm obsessed with this fluttering heart, so...
だから これでいいのら！
So, this is just fine-nora!
泣きたい から笑いたい
I want to cry, so I want to laugh
ここらだって 守ってあげるのら
I'll protect everything here-nora
だから 会いたい その願いに
So I want to see you. To that wish...
今 約束の合言葉
Now, the promised password
行くよっ！ なっしょい！
Here we go! Nasshoi!
まどろみも ホラーな夜もあるけれど でもね
There are drowsy moments and horror nights, but still...
なっしょい！
Nasshoi!
この先もみんな おりゅから平気
From now on, everyone is here, so I'm okay
まだ遊び足りねえのら！
I haven't played enough yet-nora!
生誕ライブ見に来てくれてありがとうなのら。
Thank you for coming to watch my birthday live.
今年は体調不良の時期もあったから
Since there were times I wasn't feeling well this year,
声が出なかったかもしれない… T o T
my voice might not have come out right... T o T
でも最後まで頑張ったのら！！ふんすっ！！
But I did my best until the very end!! *huff*!!
これからもずっとずっと姫様に贈る感謝を
I'll keep on expressing my gratitude to my Hime-sama forever and ever.
I Love You ちゅぱちゅぱ ♡ (・o・人)
I Love You *chupa chupa* ♡ (・o・人)
2025.10.10 るなんなのら♡
2025.10.10 Lunanna-nano-ra♡